news247.info 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy - News247.info

News247.info has strict policies on privacy of users and visitors in order to create a safe and secure community where people can come to search a great deal of information in many aspects of life such as health, movies, beauty, love, travel, tech and even cars, not problems with their personal information.

**Information collected by News247.info**

News247.info only collects such information as follows:

• Your non-personally-identifying information that is available through the policies of your Internet Service Provider and web browser, such as language preference, browser type, date and time of your last visit. These information is used by News247.info in research of its visitors and their potential activities on News247.info.

• Your Internet Protocol, for research and statistics purpose only.

• Your username and email address. Visitors and users can choose not to give this information to us. The information is for our database management of users and posts, for your better experience with information in News247.info. This is optional, yet it is stated that you may not reach certain sections or activities of News247.info unless you have signed in as an official user.  For example, it is necessary to put your name/username and email address to make a comment. It is certain that such information is kept highly confidential in our private servers and is under no circumstances revealed to anyone for any purpose. Especially, we do not sell information. We do not use it for any commercial purpose.

**Links to Third-party websites**

If you are linked to any other third-party websites, please pay attention to that website’s privacy policy. News247.info privacy policy is only valid within this site only. Your activities and information on third-party websites are subject to their privacy policies and are treated in accordance with their regulations. Therefore, please notice the privacy policies of websites before you link to News247.info.

**Privacy policy changes**

If there are any changes in the privacy policy of News247.info, the changes will be clearly stated in this page – Privacy – of News247.info. News247.info advises you to take regular visit to this page to check if there are any changes in the privacy policy. If you continue to use News247.infoafter a change has been stated, it means that you accept the change.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit:  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>  
**Contact**

For further information and questions about the privacy policy, please contact us via admin@news247.info
